(Support Admin Watch on
kissasia.cam or kisskh.org)
I know the truth now
about what the killer wants.
Besides offering sacrifices to ghosts,
that ritual also forces the ghost
to do what it wants.
You must’ve messed with something bad.
Worst case, it’s not just us in danger.
Anyone close to us could be dragged in too.
Anuphap Bunprim.
I want to know where his parents are.
There was a nurse with that last name.
Her friends called her Chaba.
The ghost Auntie saw,
was its mouth split wide like this?
This one?
You.
You’re coming with me.
Thup.
Run.
Thup, run.
Don’t stick your nose in my business.
What happened?
The same ghost.
It attacked me and Auntie Srijan.
But something saved me.
(Goddess Bless You From Death)
What you’re rushing for is,
going to see Thup, right?
If it’s nothing urgent, talk tomorrow.
I’ve got something important, Singha.
I need a word.
Just you and me.
Thup.
Wait in the room first.
I’ll follow.
I think we should head back to Bangkok.
You should question Ta Khuean yourself.
You deserve the credit in this case.
Your dad won’t let me cut in front of you.
I’m serious.
Because last time, I couldn’t protect you.
But this time,
I’ll do everything to protect you.
What the hell are you talking about?
Making my dad happy matters too.
But do you know,
there’s one thing
that’s never changed for me?
It’s you.
Do you remember?
What’s this?
Happy birthday.
Come here. Let me put it on you.
From now on,
I’ll wear the watch you gave me.
To prove I’ll protect you.
Why the hell would you wear this damn watch?
I told you to throw it away a long time ago.
How could I throw it away?
When this watch,
is our promise to protect each other.
Protect what, damn it?
If I hadn’t agreed to your transfer back then,
my dad would’ve framed you and kicked you out.
I didn’t want you to lose what you loved.
I thought back then,
that choosing this would make
everything go back to normal.
But it was the worst decision of my life.
Don’t waste time talking about the past.
It’s already over.
Our memories,
you can just throw them away like that?
The memories between you and me,
they never disappeared.
But the scars,
the ones you left on me,
they never disappeared either.
But I love you.
King.
Listen to me.
If back then you’d told me
what your dad was going to do,
we could’ve fought it together.
There were so damn many ways.
But you chose that one.
But now,
I’ve moved on.
I don’t care what you think.
You and me,
we can only be friends.
Fine.
I’ll be your friend.
That’s better than being nothing
in your life.
Aren’t you going to ask me,
what we talked about just now?
I won’t ask.
I trust you.
But your face doesn’t say that.
It’s okay.
You came back to me now.
That means you chose me.
That’s enough.
From now on, you don’t have to worry.
I’ve handled everything.
Run.
(Chanting)
The deceased in the morgue.
What is this, officer?
I already told you everything I know.
I want to know about the time
you were a police officer,
when you were in Sisaket.
I don’t remember.
You didn’t resign from service.
You fled because you killed your wife,
didn’t you?
Twenty-five years ago,
how exactly did your wife die?
Uncle,
Even if there’s no evidence
of what happened to your wife,
you ran from duty like this,
it’s like you’re guilty
of killing your own wife.
She died on her own.
Listen, uncle,
intent to kill your wife
gets you life in prison.
She caught you cheating
with a nurse, right?
I wasn’t cheating.
It was all a misunderstanding.
You wouldn’t listen.
One day, I just lost my temper.
I hit her a bit too hard.
I didn’t think she’d die.
And the officer named Atikun who died,
what do you know about him?
Atikun?
What?
What’s wrong?
Who said he’s dead?
That seven-bodies-on-the-tree case,
based on forensic evidence
and the police investigation,
the killer had to murder one per day.
Seven days, right?
Why?
I find it strange.
By the time it reaches day seven,
the condition of the first body,
it’d be too wrecked to hang, right?
If the killer really needs seven victims
to perform that sacrificial ritual,
then they must have a way to keep them,
or,
a cold room to preserve the bodies.
- Right?
- Uh… a cold room.
Or it could be,
A big fresh-food container.
You, Darin.
You okay?
Okay.
You sure?
Thank you.
Let’s go, Thup.
I’ll head back to Bangkok first.
Catch up soon.
Get home safe.
Come here.
What is it?
I know you’re in a rush, P’Singha.
But remember I said before heading back,
I had something I needed to ask Uncle Chai.
You sure?
You don’t need me to go down with you?
It’s okay.
I need to handle this myself.
Thought you already left for Bangkok.
I was going to.
But I had a question I needed to ask first.
Who exactly is this ghost?
Do you recognize them?
I don’t know them.
Thup, just go back to Bangkok.
Your life’s good now.
Why dig up the past?
But I need to know.
No matter how much I try to run,
I can’t escape these ghosts.
The only way is to find the truth.
I told you I don’t know. Go. Leave.
He must’ve been one of the victims.
The red thread sewn on
the mouth and eyes, it’s the same.
You stayed with the Grandmaster Monk
for a long time.
He must’ve told you something.
The other ghosts only hurt me,
they attacked Auntie Srijan,
they hurt the people close to me.
But this ghost keeps protecting me.
Who is she, really?
You must’ve messed with something bad.
That’s why a ghost won’t leave you alone.
Worst case, it’s not just you in danger,
but the people you love,
and those close to you.
will get dragged in too.
Drink it.
It’s okay.
The ritual can’t continue.
Let’s go back.
What’s wrong with you?
Acting all mysterious.
You’re scared of ghosts,
yet you still dare come to a ritual like this.
Cold?
Are you worried I’m cold,
or are you about to scold me?
Pick one. I can’t prepare my emotions.
This place might be linked
to the seven-body case.
And you still dare come here?
Ta Khuean acted alone.
That doesn’t mean this place is bad.
Besides, I’m just here for a cleansing ritual.
It’s nothing serious.
Nothing serious?
What if something happened
after you drank that water?
Then what?
- I didn’t think,
- Don’t argue.
I think you believe in this stuff too much.
So much you’re risking your own life.
And the water you bathed in,
who knows if it’s contaminated.
I’m going to change clothes.
I don’t want to fight with you.
After your grandma,
left you with the Grandmaster Monk,
he ordered that nothing be told to you,
about your family,
about your home,
because he was afraid,
you’d be put in danger.
The picture you drew,
that one, Dao,
that’s your mother, Thup.
Your mother,
was a kept woman of a police officer.
She hoped that,
after giving birth to you,
your father would leave his main family
and come live with the two of you.
But that’s how it goes,
men’s true nature.
After that,
he stopped caring about either of you.
So your mother,
quit her job as a teacher,
planning to move somewhere else,
not wanting to be people’s gossip,
and then this happened first.
Mom… Mom…
What is it? Blood,
Please take care of my child.
Go now, Mom.
Please
Please don’t.
Good thing,
your grandma found you
and brought you to the Grandmaster Monk,
for your safety.
Grandmaster Monk,
please take my grandson in and look after him.
From now on, your name is,
Thup.
So how exactly did my mother die?
Some said it was her ex-husband.
Others said it was black magic.
But in the end,
the villagers
found your mother’s body
in a sacrificial ritual.
Her mouth and eyes were sewn shut,
just like that case.
Run, Thup.
Thup, run.
Don’t hurt my child.
As for your father,
whether he was the one who did it,
I’m not sure.
Then who is my father?
Your father was a former police officer.
But he died a long time ago.
They said his name was,
Atikun.
What Ta Khuean said just now,
it sounded strange.
Like Officer Atikun isn’t actually dead.
Who are you calling, Captain?
P’Sing.
How did the officer named Atikun die?
Seemed like illness.
A quiet ceremony at home.
No one from the station attended.
So no one ever saw the body, right?
Probably.
Why?
Because what Ta Khuean said earlier,
it sounded like Atikun isn’t dead.
Like there’s some kind of plan.
Then keep questioning Ta Khuean for me.
If he really faked his death,
Ta Khuean might be involved.
And that person might be connected
to Santi Tham House in some way.
I’ll head back right away.
Got it.
So? Did you find anything?
I found what was bothering me.
Good.
Then we’re heading back to Bangkok.
There’s a suspect who may have faked his death,
using his status as a former cop
to cover his tracks.
A former cop?
Yes.
His name is Sergeant Atikun.
He was the husband of a nurse named Chaba.
Thup.
What’s wrong, Thup?
Sergeant Atikun,
is my father.
Darin.
Next time,
don’t sneak off alone again.
And why did you follow me?
Worried about me, huh?
What?
What now?
Power cables.
Cooling pipes.
Look, there’s cold air coming out.
Hey, I think we should go back.
Salt.
Darin.
- What?
- Is this a cold room?
Yeah.
Why build a cold room here?
Let’s go.
You don’t have to feel bad.
Either way, we need the truth
to prove the evidence.
Maybe Atikun really is dead.
Or,
he and your father
might be two different people.
And if he really did it,
how am I supposed to feel,
having a father who’s a killer,
who killed who knows how many,
and even killed my mother,
and tried to kill me too?
What would you do?
You and your father,
are not the same person.
But I can’t deny the truth,
that I’m connected to him.
Either way, he’s my family.
Family,
doesn’t mean sharing the same DNA.
It means people who love each other,
who are bonded, who trust each other.
So that Atikun,
is definitely not your family.
Your family,
is me.
You’re really that confident in me?
You’re a good person.
I’ve trusted you all along.
No matter who your father is,
it doesn’t change
what people see in you, Thup.
You’re so good to me,
I’ll save up and replace the ring for you.
No need.
This way it’s cool, one of a kind.
But if people find out
we’re using the Phirot Ring as a couple ring,
they’ll think we’re weird,
considering where we found it.
This way fits just right.
Come here.
Don’t overthink it.
- Please wait here for a moment.
- Sure.
What’s going on, officer?
Hello, sir.
We’ll need to trouble you
to conduct another search here.
We’ve received new information,
there may be another suspect
working with Ta Khuean,
possibly connected to Santi Tham House.
They may be hiding here,
so we need to search.
Search whatever you need.
Just don’t disturb
the practitioners here.
Thank you.
Then I’ll need to collect DNA samples,
from you, and from all male disciples
who work here.
Go ahead.
You can’t do that, officer.
You can’t make accusations
without evidence.
A virtuous, moral person like him,
- how could he do such a thing?
- That’s enough.
Hello to all fellow practitioners.
Please share this widely.
The police are harassing people of virtue.
This really is the dark age
of uniformed bandits.
We’re just doing our duty.
We really need your cooperation.
- Get out, you demons of religion!
- Yeah, go! Get out!
- Get out!
- We don’t want you here!
Let’s come back another time.
Then I’ll take my leave for now.
- Go! He’s a good man!
- Yeah, go! Get out!
- Please leave!
- Go back!
Sey, Darin, how did you end up here?
Darin’s a disciple here.
He just came for some kind of cleansing ritual.
And you, Captain, what are you doing here?
Go! Get out, you demons of religion!
Get out!
Leave the way you came.
- We’re leaving!
- Get out!
- So hot-headed. How do you even practice?
- Keep filming.
Why did the police have to search
Santi Tham House?
That’s something Inspector King
and other officers,
cannot comment on.
Because as of now,
I have personally taken over this case.
At this moment, the police
have arrested the suspect,
Mr. Khuean,
the manager of Santi Tham House.
He was taken into custody days ago.
And once the investigation,
and all evidence are fully established,
Mr. Khuean will be forwarded,
to court for further proceedings.
So Mr. Khuean is the killer, right?
The evidence is clear, correct?
Here.
(Instant relief, stick it on.)
You, seriously.
Hello?
Have you seen the news about my dad?
What news?
What did your dad do now?
Just see it yourself.
Mr. Montat Boonkhingklai,
the suspect in the
seven-bodies-on-the-tree case,
has died in custody.
Police believe the deceased
may have feared prosecution.
Is that true, sir?
- Was this a scapegoat, sir?
- That’s right.
Yes, what about it, sir?
Hey, everyone, calm down.
Are you sure,
this wasn’t your dad’s doing,
killing our only lead?
You get that, right?
You can’t do this, sir.
I’ve already signed off to close this case.
You and King are dismissed.
How many more people have to die
as scapegoats, sir,
before you realize
what a police officer’s real duty is?
A police officer’s duty,
is to keep the country under control,
to prevent chaos.
And that’s exactly what I’m doing.
Yes, sir.
Not running around meddling,
until everything spirals out of control
like you did.
A good police officer’s job,
is to catch criminals
and bring them to justice.
As for how you get them,
the public doesn’t really care.
Before long, they’ll forget.
These days, the internet keeps evidence.
Aren’t you afraid people will figure it out later,
that you fooled them just for appearances?
This time, just dismissing you,
I don’t think that’ll be enough.
Don’t worry.
You won’t be doing this job much longer.
Because power,
lies at the tip of the pen that signs.
I told you already, didn’t I,
there’s no place for cops like you here.
Just wait and see.
What happened?
They pulled me off the case.
But as long as I’m still alive,
I’ll keep investigating.
Whether Ta Khuean is the killer or not,
you already know,
there isn’t just one culprit.
So what are you going to do next?
If you really are Atiyakhun’s son,
we should be able to match your DNA.
And if Atiyakhun isn’t dead,
you’re the only lead.
P’Sing.
I’ve sent it to the lab
and asked them to rush the test.
Yes. I’ll let you know
as soon as the results are out.
Got it.
What are you doing?
Don’t tell me,
you booked another cleansing ritual
or some exorcism course again.
No.
I’m looking at this.
This is,
the same logo we found at Santi Tham House.
It’s an industrial cooling unit.
Santi Tham House shouldn’t need something like this.
But is the temperature low enough to store bodies?
Ai Song.
- How’s it going? Still a lot left?
- Not much. Almost done.
That’s a long one.
What do you want to eat after this?
What are you doing?
Sorry, man, Ai Song.
Hello?
The lab results are out.
Thup’s DNA,
matches someone.
Who?
Someone from Santi Tham House?
No.
A kid named Bom.
Who?
Bom.
The YouTuber you arrested before.
I kept his DNA on file.
Thup’s DNA matches Bom’s.
Thup and Bom,
might be related.
Or someone in the family.
Or maybe,
they could be siblings.
How can a cop fall for a killer’s kid?
Who said that? I’ll punch his mouth.
The Mae Sue has made amends.
Inviting Wichitramawanna to descend.
So both were born on Sunday.
The next one is Monday.
Since getting back from Sisaket,
you haven’t rested.
Victims can’t wait.
Cops don’t get to rest.
I think it’s definitely their work.
You think there’s something in the cold room?
If the killer used this method
and the victim isn’t dead yet,
we might still make it in time to save them.
I said we should live together.
Casting a charm so
the husband loves and adores her.
You can tell this is a Naga medium,
half the body in water.
(Naga spirit possession)
And the other half,
the lower half is still human,
then it turns into a snake.
- Down there it’s a snake now.
- Okay.
I need to talk.
Just you and me.
You’ll get punched for sure.
When you turn around, it might be like,
“No, I trust you,” something like that.
You’re not going to ask what we talked about?
I won’t ask.
I trust you.
(But the tone doesn’t match.)